<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="WeightDistroDsc">
        Front Weight Distribution (e.g. Weight) percentage can be found the game when upgrading your car.
        In the \"Upgrades and Tuning\" -> \"Custom Upgrade\" look in the left \"information\" box when
        installing new parts.
        \n\n
        Typically, it is advised to keep your car as light as possible, but that might not always
        be the case for You. Sometimes weight can help with the grip for the rear-wheel-drive cars.
        \n\n
        Rebound Stiffness, Springs and Anti-Roll Bars calculated with the following formula:\n
        \n
        <b>Front: [(Max - Min) * (FW / 100)] + Min = EV\n</b>
        <b>Rear: [(Max - Min) * (RW% / 100)] + Min = EV\n</b>
        \n

        \"Max and Min\" are the Maximum and Minimum possible adjustable values available for the field
        you estimating settings of. Move field\'s slider all the way to the left (for Min) and to the right
        (for Max).\n\n
        FW - Front Weight Distribution (e.g. in-game weight value).\n\n
        RW - Rear Weight Distribution (e.g. \"100 - FrontWeight\").\n\n
        EV - Calculated Estimated Value.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="MinValueDsc">
        Minimum adjustable value available for the field you are tuning. (move slider in the game all
        the way to the left to get that number).
    </string>


    <string name="MaxValueDsc">
        Maximum adjustable value available for the field you are tuning. (move slider in the game all
        the way to the right to get that number).
    </string>


    <string name="EstimatedValueDsc">
        Estimated value gives you a starting tuning point based of your car properties. Start micro-tuning
        from here by adjusting the value left and right and test the effects on your car until you
        get what you want.
    </string>


    <string name="ReboundDsc">
        Rebound and Bump Stiffness controls how your car reacts to the uneven and bumpy roads. If you
        are losing control when driving through uneven roads - adjust Rebound and Bump stiffness.\n\n
        Lowering Front Rebound Stiffness can help reduce Understeer.\n
        Decrease Rear Rebound Stiffness to reduce Oversteer.\n\n
        Front and Rear Bump Stiffness values are between 50 and 70 percent of Front and Rear Rebound
        Stiffness estimated values.\n\n
        Increasing Front bump stiffness helps to reduce Understeer problems.\n
        When car is Unstable at high speed: adjust between Min and Max for both Front and Rear relative
        to your current Rebound Stiffness.
    </string>


    <string name="BumpDsc">
        Front and Rear values are between 50 and 70 percent of Front and Rear Rebound Stiffness estimated
        value.\n
        Increasing Front bump stiffness helps to reduce Understeer problems.\n
        When car is Unstable at high speed: adjust between Min and Max for both Front and Rear relative
        to your current Rebound Stiffness.
    </string>


    <string name="SpringsDsc">
        In-game description says it all. Using the same formula to estimate Front and Rear base values.\n
        \n
        Soften(decrease) Front Springs to reduce Understeer.\n
        When car is Unstable at high speed: softening(decreasing) Front Springs may help stabilize it.
    </string>


    <string name="AntiRollDsc">
        In-game description says it all. Estimated value gives you a baseline to start your tuning from.\n
        \n
        Soften(decrease) Front Anti Roll helps reduce Understeer.\n
        Soften(decrease) Rear Ani Roll helps reduce Oversteer.
    </string>

</resources>