<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="WeightDistroDsc">
        Front Weight Distribution percentage.\n
        This value can be found below the "Weight" value in the information box when installing new
        parts in the "Upgrades and Tuning" -> "Custom Upgrade".
        \n\n
        Typically, it is advised to keep your car as light as possible, but that might not always
        be the case for You. Sometimes weight can help with the grip for the rear-wheel-drive cars.
        \n\n
        Rebound Stiffness, Springs and Anti-Roll Bars calculated with the following formula:\n
        Front: [(Max - Min) * (Front Weight% / 100)] + Min = estimated value\n
        Rear: [(Max - Min) * (Rear Weight% / 100)] + Min = estimated value\n
        \n
        "Max and Min" are the Maximum and Minimum possible adjustable values available for the field
        you estimating settings of.\n

        "Rear Weight" is (100 - Front Weight%). So if your Front Weight Distribution is 55%, Rear Weight
        is 45%.
        \n\n
        Bump Stiffness is explained in the In Game description. It is a value between 50-75% of calculated
        Rebound Stiffness for the Front and Rear.
    </string>

    <string name="MinValueDsc">
        Minimum adjustable value available for the field you are tuning. (move slider in the game all
        the way to the left to get that number).
    </string>


    <string name="MaxValueDsc">
        Maximum adjustable value available for the field you are tuning. (move slider in the game all
        the way to the right to get that number).
    </string>


    <string name="EstimatedValueDsc">
        Estimated value gives you a starting tuning point based of your car properties. Start micro-tuning
        from here by adjusting the value left and right and test the effects on your car until you
        get what you want.
    </string>


    <string name="ReboundDsc">
        Rebound and Bump Stiffness controls how your car reacts to the uneven and bumpy roads. If you
        are losing control when driving through uneven roads - tune Rebound and Dump stiffness.\n
        \n
        Lowering Front Rebound Stiffness can help reduce Understeer.\n
        Decrease Rear Rebound Stiffness to reduce Oversteer.\n
    </string>


    <string name="BumpDsc">
        Front and Rear values are between 50 and 70 percent of Front and Rear Rebound Stiffness estimated
        value.\n
        Increasing Front bump stiffness helps to reduce Understeer problems.\n
        When car is Unstable at high speed: adjust between Min and Max for both Front and Rear relative
        to your current Rebound Stiffness.
    </string>


    <string name="SpringsDsc">
        In Game description says it all. Using the same formula(check Weight Distribution info button)
        to estimate Front and Rear base values. Estimated value gives you a baseline to start tuning
        from.\n
        \n
        Soften(decrease) Front Springs to reduce Understeer.\n
        When car is Unstable at high speed: softening(decreasing) Front Springs may help stabilize it.
    </string>


    <string name="AntiRollDsc">
        In Game description says it all. Estimated value gives you a baseline to start tuning from.\n
        \n
        Soften(decrease) Front Anti Roll helps reduce Understeer.\n
        Soften(decrease) Rear Ani Roll helps reduce Oversteer.
    </string>

</resources>